That everyday cash option I hope you will be doing very well
so friends in today's video
we will talk to you
about job vacancy of ICICI Lombard Process
this job vacancy is for Mumbai location
so in this UK we will talk about
how to apply what is celebrity
credit what celebrities you will meet we will
talk about all of them in detail so
let's get started before we start I would
like to request all of you that
if you haven't subscribed to our channel yet then you
can subscribe to this video channel by clicking on the subscribe button
so that I don't miss any video notifications so guys
as I
told you earlier that ICICI's number is solid
for this job vacancy debit is that the
insurance custom of the ad where this job vacancy comes out
this job vacancy this
invite is in the call center but mounted
you will have to attend the card here whether it is
prescription work or the basic work of the job
it will be customer services that means
you have to provide service to the customer you have to
tell the customer about the services
through them this app can get its target  It is possible
because this Noor will be a little special for you in a way,
Sanskrit, so all these
things that you have to do here, if you
want to apply here, then the minimum
qualification is that
you can apply even if you are 12th pass, if you have a
cigarette separation then you will get Prince, please pay
attention to your nature, you
can apply but the best ones are going to get this
reference, so
whoever is interested, you will get the address below the video, the
address in which is work in the
earthquake, this work in Hindi means the
nearby address is in Navi Mumbai,
now people can go directly and
give the walking interview, till when will this interview
continue, there is no permission date for it, if it will be today
then I will
mention it in the description of the video, but right now it
is August, whenever you are watching the video, that is, I am
putting it in the video right now,
this interview will continue till 2030, if
someone used to get commission in the date, I will
put it in the description below the video, whoever is
interested,  Now you
can go and give a walking interview quickly. Apart from this,
if you remember about Mumbai, Dubai
rumors, jobs questions anywhere for Mumbai,
Sab TV's customer service
sensitive temperature, then definitely subscribe to this channel.
According to the day, we keep
bringing new job related videos on this channel.
Right now, the
salary of this job, no SMS has been sent here,
but the April Kshatriya is of 15 to
20 thousand rupees, everything can be fine, you can
apply for press flat bench here,
but if you have experience, then
you will get the opportunity here, if
all the documents of Express are fine, if
you like, there will be romance, only
then will you get the exchange, there will be no pressure
because it depends on Express, whatever
explanation you can give, it was good, that
sandwich is often available, so for experience, it is
necessary to have a 10 year certificate,
so whoever is interested, give it quickly
within an hour, I will mention all the details
in the description below the video.
That's all in your bedroom, if
you have any doubt related to the job, you
can comment in the comment box below, if
you want to talk to us about anything related to any job,
then you can go to the
temple of humanity in the description of the video and
message in the appointments, then the
rainy birds will fly towards you and the meeting will
start very well